[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Speaker 1: Hello, thank you for calling PetSmart customers here.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] This is Paula, to whom do I have the pleasure of speaking?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Hi, my name is Jolie Kor, and I'm just go ahead.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I was going to say hi, Jolie.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Hi.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Do you need other information from me?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Yes, your email address and phone number, please.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] My email is jolle.co96 at yahoo.com.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] My phone number is 971-344-7099.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Awesome.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thank you very much for that.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] How can I help you tonight, Jolie?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I was just calling to see what we can do about my auto-ship order.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] It says it's expired and that it's undeliverable.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] So I think it needs like re-sent out with Roadie or FedEx, whichever one.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] But this is the second time it's happened now.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Oh, no.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Let me see here.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Why are they not delivering this?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I'm not sure.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I've gotten packages from PetSmart like through the normal deliveries through Rhodi just funds, but this is my first auto-ship order, and it's just not working very well.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] People are picking up the gig and then canceling it or not doing it.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] This doesn't make sense.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I don't get it.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] All right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Well, I could reship it a third time, or I could refund it.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Which would you prefer?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] I would prefer to have it sent out again.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] All right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Almost finished.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] All right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] That has been processed and it should arrive in the next one to three days.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Okay.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thank you.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] You are welcome.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Is there anything else I can do to help you and your puppy dogs connect?
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] That will be all.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] All right.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Well, thank you for calling PetSmart.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] And I hope you have a wonderful evening.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] You as well.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Bye-bye.
[speaker_SPEAKER_00] Thank you.